TWUA Photographs 6924 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Oversize strike, portrait, and other photographs, black and white photograph (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 40: John Chupka, general secretary-treasurer, TWUA., black and white photograph (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Fabian Bachrach [photographer]. Gelatin silver print, 1950? Image depicts Chupka in a three-quarter length pose, holding a cigarette in his right hand; photo taken in a studio setting. Chupka was general secretary-treasurer of the TWUA from at least 1951 to at least 1959. 18.5 x 23.5 cm. (w/out mount); 26 x 33.5 cm. (w/mount).
  - Item 41: William Pollock (1899-1982), general president of TWUA, 1956-1972., black and white photograph (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Fabian Bachrach [photographer]. Gelatin silver print, 196-? Image depicts Pollock from chest up, wearing suit and tie; photo taken in studio setting. See item 33 in this folder for a photo of Pollock as a younger man. 18.5 x 23.5 cm. (w/out mount); 26 x 33.5 cm. (w/mount).